Finding aid for the Universal Pictures Corporation Walter Lantz Productions scripts and music cue sheets, ca. 1947-1987 (bulk 1947-1965) LSC.1969
UCLA Library Special Collections
Universal Pictures Corporation Walter Lantz Productions scripts and music cue sheets
circa 1947-1987
bulk 1947-1965
UCLA Library Special Collections
Universal Pictures Corporation
LSC.1969
3 Linear Feet (6 boxes)
Walter Lantz was an American cartoonist who is best remembered for the mischievous Woody the Woodpecker, a popular character who for many years appeared in cartoon shorts for theatres, and later on television. Universal Pictures bought the library of shorts and the rights to Walter Lantz productions in mid-1980s. The collection contains original and copies of continuity scripts and copies of revised music cue sheets related to Walter Lantz cartoons productions under the ownership of Universal Pictures.
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Gift of Gift of Universal Pictures, 2009.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9970921763606533
Biography
Universal bought the library of shorts and the rights to Walter Lantz productions in mid-1980s. Lantz remained active in overseeing how Universal handled his characters (for merchandise, TV, home video, theme parks, limited edition cels, etc.) up until his death in 1994.
Walter Lantz was an American cartoonist who is best remembered for the mischievous Woody the Woodpecker. In 1929, Lantz was hired to run the new cartoon unit at Universal Pictures and took over directing the Oswald the Rabbit series. In 1935, Lantz started his own studio Walter Lantz Productions, producing cartoons for Universal. In about 1940, the Lantz-Universal partnership was dissolved; shortly after, Woody the Woodpecker was born. After pairing Woody with Andy Panda for three projects, Woody became Lantz's flagship character for many years appearing in cartoon shorts for theatres, and later on television.
Lantz created other cartoon characters such as Chilly Willy, the Beary Family, and Inspector Willoughby. Some of these characters were produced as a "Walter Lantz Cartune." From 1947-1948, United Artists distributed Lantz productions until, due to financial considerations, his studio closed. A year later, he reunited with Universal Pictures (then called Universal International) and reopened his studio. The Woody Woodpecker Show ran on television from 1957 to 1958. In 1970, it reappeared on Saturday mornings with twenty-six additional half-hours featuring Lantz's post-1948 cartoons; it was then later syndicated. Before closing his studio in 1972, Lantz succeeded in becoming the most active producer of theatrical cartoon shorts.
Scope and Content
The collection consists of original and copies of continuity scripts and copies of revised music cue sheets related to Walter Lantz cartoons productions under the ownership of Universal Pictures. It appears the scripts in the collection represent television and theatrical short productions, featuring characters such as Woody Woodpecker, Andy Panda, Beary Family, Chilly Willy, Doc and Champ, Gabby Gator, and Inspector Willoughby. Some of the scripts are credited as a "Walter Lantz Cartune." The music cue sheets are for the Woody Woodpecker television program. Additionally, there is a loose bound binder titled Oswald that contains photocopies of: synopses, character illustrations, articles, a small number of photographs and transparencies, and a brief piece by Walter Lantz, titled "How to Make Cartoons."
Organization and Arrangement
There is no specific arrangement to the collection.
Related Material
Walter Lantz Productions Collection of Music for Woody Woodpecker Cartoons and Other Productions (Collection PASC 35).
Walter Lantz Animation Archive (Collection PASC 47).
Animated films -- Archives.; Universal Pictures Corporation; Walter Lantz Productions -- Archives.
- Ballyhooey - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1960 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  General note
  Walter Lantz Woody Woodpecker cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-110.
- Bats in the Belfry - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1960 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  Walter Lantz Woody Woodpecker cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-112.
- Bear and the Bees - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1961 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  Walter Lantz cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-126.
- Billion Dollar Boner - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1960 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  Walter Lantz Woody Woodpecker cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-107.
- Bird Who Came to Dinner (The) - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1961 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  Walter Lantz Woody Woodpecker cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-122.
- Busman's Holiday - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1961 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  Walter Lantz Woody Woodpecker cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-131.
- Calling Dr. Woodpecker - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1963 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  Walter Lantz Woody Woodpecker cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-146.
- Canned Dog Feud - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1964 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  Walter Lantz Woody Woodpecker cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-193.
- Careless Caretaker - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1962 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  Walter Lantz Woody Woodpecker cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-150.
- Case of the Cold Storage Yegg - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1963 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  Walter Lantz Inspector Willoughby cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-159.
- Case of the Elephant's Trunk (The) - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1964 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  Walter Lantz Inspector Willoughby cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-188.
- Case of the Maltese Chicken (The) - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1964 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  Walter Lantz Inspector Willoughby cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-176.
- Case of the Red-eyed Ruby - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1961 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  Walter Lantz Inspector Willoughby cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-134.
- Charlie's Mother-in-law - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1963 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  Walter Lantz The Beary's cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U- 161.
- Clash and Carry - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1961 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  Walter Lantz Chilly Willy cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U- 128.
- Coming Out Party - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1962 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  Walter Lantz Inspector Willoughby cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-158.
- Corny Concerto - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1962 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  Walter Lantz Doc and Champ cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-157.
- Coy Decoy - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1963 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  Walter Lantz Woody Woodpecker cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-166.
- Davey Cricket - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1964 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  Walter Lantz Beary Family cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-196.
- Deep Freeze Squeeze - dialogue and cutting continuity script, c. 1964 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  Walter Lantz Chilly Willy cartoon. Original envelope annotated U- 177.
- Dialogue and scene continuity scripts (folder 1 of 4), c. 1947, c. 1949, no date (Box 3, Folder 2)
  Dog Tax Dodgers, Playful Pelican, Scrappy Birthday, Sky Dogs, Wet Blanket Policy, and Wild and Woody. Walter Lantz cartoon and Walter Lantz Woody Woodpecker cartoon. UA-Nos. 8-12 and C-11. Each title includes two copies. Original envelope annotated UA-8 thru UA-12, 1000-1002-1003-1007-1008, C-2 - C-12, A-997.
- Dialogue and scene continuity scripts (folder 2 of 4), no date (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Fun House, Goofy Roofer, Toyland Army, Village Blacksmith, and Woody's Jalopy. 1000, 1002, 1003, 1007, and 1008. Some titles include two copies. Original envelope annotated UA-8 thru UA-12, 1000-1002-1003-1007-1008, C-2 - C-12, A-97
- Dialogue and scene continuity scripts (folder 3 of 4), no date (Box 3, Folder 4)
  The Gas Bandit and Springtime For Andy. C-2 and C-12. Each title includes two copies. Original envelope annotated UA-8 thru UA-12, 1000-1002-1003-1007-1008, C-2 - C-12, A-997.
- Dialogue and scene continuity scripts (folder 4 of 4), no date (Box 3, Folder 5)
  Dizzy Kitty. A-997. Two copies. Original envelope annotated UA-8 thru UA-12, 1000-1002-1003-1007-1008, C-2 - C-12, A-997.
- Doc's Last Stand - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1961 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  Walter Lantz cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-139
- Dumb Like a Fox - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1964 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  Walter Lantz Woody Woodpecker cartoon, Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-174.
- Eggnapper - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1961 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  Walter Lantz cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-121
- Fish and Chips - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, no date (Box 4, Folder 27)
  Walter Lantz Chilly Willy cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U- 155.
- Fish Hooked - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1960 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  Walter Lantz Chilly Willy cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U- 114.
- Fowled Up Falcon - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1960 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  Walter Lantz Woody Woodpecker cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-117.
- Fowled-up Birthday - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1962 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  Walter Lantz cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-151
- Fractured Friendship - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1964 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  Walter Lantz Chilly Willy cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U- 189.
- Franken-stymied - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1961 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  Walter Lantz Woody Woodypecker cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-129.
- Freeloading Feline - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1960 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  Walter Lantz cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-116.
- Freeway Fracas - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1964 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  Walter Lantz Woody Woodpecker cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-183.
- Gabby's Diner - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1961 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  Walter Lantz Woody Woodpecker cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-124.
- Get Lost! Little Dog - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1964 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  Walter Lantz Woody Woodpecker cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-182.
- Goose in the Rough - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1963 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  Walter Lantz The Beary's cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U- 167.
- Goose is Wild - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1963 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  Walter Lantz The Beary Family cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-171.
- Greedy Gabby Gator - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1963 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  Walter Lantz Woody Woodpecker cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-156.
- Growin' Pains - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1962 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  Walter Lantz Woody Woodpecker cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-142.
- Guest Who? - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1964 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  Walter Lantz Beary Family cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-192.
- Half Baked Alaska - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1964 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  Walter Lantz Chilly Willy cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U- 194.
- Heap Big Hepcat - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1959 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  Walter Lantz Woody Woodpecker cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-109.
- Hi-seas Hi-jacker - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1963 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  Walter Lantz Inspector Willoughby cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-163.
- How to Stuff a Woodpecker - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1960 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  Walter Lantz Woody Woodpecker cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-111.
- Hunger Strife - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1960 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  Walter Lantz cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-113.
- Hyde and Sneak - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1962 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  Walter Lantz Inspector Willoughby cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-149.
- Janie Get Your Gun - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1964 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  Walter Lantz Woody Woodpecker cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-195.
- Kiddie League - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1959 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  Walter Lantz Woody Woodpecker cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-105.
- Lighthouse Keeping Blues - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1964 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  Walter Lantz Chilly Willy cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U- 181.
- Little Woody Riding Hood - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1962 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  Walter Lantz Woody Woodpecker cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-154.
- Mackerel Moocher - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1962 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  Walter Lantz Chilly Willy cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U- 147.
- Mississippi Slow Boat - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1961 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  Walter Lantz cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-130.
- Mother's Little Helper - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1962 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  Walter Lantz cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-153.
- Mouse Trapped - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1959 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  Walter Lantz cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-104
- Oswald binder (folder 1 of 2), no date (Box 6, Folder 4)
  Binder removed for preservation purposes. With photocopies of articles and character drawings from the late 1920s to 1930s.
- Oswald binder (folder 2 of 2), no date (Box 6, Folder 5)
  Binder removed for preservation purposes. Photocopies of articles and character drawings from the late 1920s to 1930s, How to Make Animated Cartoons by Walter Lantz, and photographic material.
- Ozark Lark - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1960 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  Walter Lantz Woody Woodpecker cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-115.
- Papoose on the Loose - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1961 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  Walter Lantz cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-123.
- Pesky Pelican - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, no date (Box 5, Folder 2)
  Walter Lantz Chilly Willy cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U- 168.
- Pest of Show - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1962 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  Walter Lantz cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-143,
- Pesty Guest - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1965 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  Walter Lantz Chilly Willy cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U- 198.
- Phantom of the Horse Opera - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1961 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  Walter Lantz Woody Woodpecker cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-135.
- Phoney Express - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1962 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  Walter Lantz Inspector Willoughby cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-141.
- Pistol Packin' Woodpecker - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1960 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  Walter Lantz Woody Woodpecker cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-108.
- Poop Deck Pirate - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1961 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  Walter Lantz Woody Woodpecker cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-120.
- Punch Pooch - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1962 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  Walter Lantz Doc and Champ cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-145.
- Rah Rah Ruckus - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1964 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  Walter Lantz The Beary's Family cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-180.
- Roamin' Roman - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1964 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  Walter Lantz Woody Woodpecker cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-186.
- Robin Hoody Woody - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1962 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  Walter Lantz Woody Woodpecker cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-160.
- Rock-A-Bye Gator - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1962 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  Walter Lantz Woody Woodpecker cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-136.
- Rocket Racket - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1962 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  Walter Lantz Woody Woodpecker cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-148.
- Roof Top Razzle-Dazzle - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1964 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  Walter Lantz Beary Family cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-184.
- Room and Bored - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1962 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  Walter Lantz Woody Woodpecker cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-140.
- Rough and Tumbleweed - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1961 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  Walter Lantz cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-118.
- Saddle-Sore Woody - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1964 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  Walter Lantz Woody Woodpecker cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-178.
- Salmon Loafer - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1963 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  Walter Lantz Chilly Willy cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U- 165.
- Science Fiction - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1963 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  Walter Lantz Woody Woodpecker cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-173.
- Shutter Bug - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1963 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  Walter Lantz Woody Woodpecker cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-164.
- Sioux Me - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1964 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  Walter Lantz Woody Woodpecker cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-197.
- Ski-napper - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1964 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  Walter Lantz Chilly Willy cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U- 185.
- Skinfolks - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1964 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  Walter Lantz Woody Woodpecker cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-179.
- Southern Fried Hospitality - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1960 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  Walter Lantz Woody Woodpecker cartoon with Gabby Gator. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-119.
- Space Mouse - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1959 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  Walter Lantz cartoon (2 copies). Original envelope annotated U-103.
- St. Moritz Blitz - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1961 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  Walter Lantz Chilly Willy cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U- 125.
- Stowaway Woody - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1963 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  Walter Lantz Woody Woodpecker cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-162.
- Sufferin' Cats - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1961 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  Walter Lantz Woody Woodpecker cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-127.
- Tee Pee For Two - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1963 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  Walter Lantz Woody Woodpecker cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-172.
- Three Little Woodpeckers - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1964 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  Walter Lantz Woody Woodpecker cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-187.
- Tin Tan Concert - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1961 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  Walter Lantz cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-137.
- Tragic Magic - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1962 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  Walter Lantz Woody Woodpecker cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-144.
- Tricky Trout - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1961 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  Walter Lantz Chilly Willy cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U- 132.
- Voo-Doo Boo-Boo - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1962 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  Walter Lantz Woody Woodpecker cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-152.
- Walter Lantz cartoon and Walter Lantz Woody Woodpecker cartoon - cutting and dialogue continuity scripts (folder 1 of 6), c. 1951-1952, c. 1954-1956 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  After The Ball, Chief Charlie Horse, Dig That Dog, A Fine Feathered Frenzy, Real Gone Woody, The Tree Medic, Witch Crafty, Woodpecker in the Rough, and The Woody Woodpecker Polka. Some titles include two copies. U-Nos. 6, 10, 29, 33, 36, 42, 52- 53, and 58.
- Walter Lantz cartoon and Walter Lantz Woody Woodpecker cartoon - cutting and dialogue continuity scripts (folder 2 of 6), c. 1956-1957 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  Arts and Flowers, The Big Snooze, Box Car Bandit, Calling All Cuckoos, Dopey Dick, Fodder and Son, The Goofy Gardener, Swiss Miss-fit, and Woody Meets Davy Crewcut. U-Nos. 60, 62, 66, 71, and 75-79.
- Walter Lantz cartoon and Walter Lantz Woody Woodpecker cartoon - cutting and dialogue continuity scripts (folder 3 of 6), c. 1957-1960 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  Billion Dollar Bones, The Bongo Punch, Everglade Raid, Little Televillain, Mouse Trapped, Pistol Packin' Woodpecker, Salmon Yeggs, Space Mouse, Truant Student, Witty Kitty, and Woodpecker in the Moon. With Walter Lantz cartoon with Windy and Breezy, Truant Student and a Walter Lantz Chilly Willy cartoon, Little Televillain. U- Nos. 81, 84, 89, 94, 96, 102-104, and 106-108.
- Walter Lantz cartoon and Walter Lantz Woody Woodpecker cartoon - cutting and dialogue continuity scripts (folder 4 of 6), c. 1960-1962, c. 1964 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  Doc's Last Stand, Freeloading Feline, Gabby's Diner, Papoose on the Loose, Roamin' Roman, Three Little Woodpeckers, and Tin Can Concert. Some scripts are duplicates. With Walter Lantz Inspector Willoughby cartoon, Hyde and Sneak and a Walter Lantz Chilly Willy cartoon, Fish and Chips. U-Nos. 116, 123-124, 137, 139, 149, 155, and 186-187.
- Walter Lantz Woody Woodpecker cartoon - cutting and dialogue continuity scripts (folder 5 of 6), c. 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  Birds of a Feather, Canned Dog Feud, Janie Get Your Gun, Sioux Me, What's Peckin', and Woodpecker Wanted. Some titles include two copies. U-Nos. 190-191, 193, 195, and 199.
- Walter Lantz Woody Woodpecker cartoon - cutting and dialogue continuity scripts (folder 6 of 6), c. 1965, c. 1968 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  Astronut Woody, The Big Bite, Hassle in a Castle, A Lad in Bagdad, Lonesome Ranger, One Horse Town, Practical Yolk, Rough Riding Hood, and Woody and the Beanstalk. Some titles include two copies. U-Nos. 200-201, 203, 205, 208, 209, 211, 236, and 237.
- Woodpecker From Mars - dialogue and cutting continuity script, c. 1956 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  Walter Lantz Woody Woodpecker cartoon. Original envelope annotated U- 59.
- Woody Woodpecker - General Mills repackaging outside costs budget, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Woody Woodpecker Show (The) - cutting continuity scripts, no date (Box 2, Folder 1)